Guide to the Winston Weisman Collection of Architectural Photographs [1950]-1973 depicting structures ca. 1850 - 1970 PR 73
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Negatives
  - MANHATTAN
    This subseries begins with named streets filed alphabetically, thereunder by avenues and numbered streets numerically, and concludes with a large section of miscellaneous unidentified buildings. At the end of the subseries are two significant sets of negatives that were important to Weisman's research, Rockefeller Center and Laing Stores. This subseries ends with views and maps of Manhattan.
    - Battery Park -- 299 Broadway (Box 50)
    - 300 Broadway -- Nassau Street (Box 51)
    - Park Avenue -- Fourth Avenue (Box 52)
    - Fifth Avenue -- West 125th Street miscellaneous buildings (Box 53)
    - Rockefeller Center (Box 54)
    - Laing Stores 258 -- 262 Washington Street views of Manhattan maps (Box 55)
  - GEORGE B. POST
    This subseries consists of negatives of copy prints of miscellaneous buildings by George P. Post among the negative series. George Post (1837 -- 1913) was an important figure in the development of the skyscraper and a particular point of interest for Weisman as Post used innovative building techniques to create ever-taller buildings and large interior spaces for public use. Significant buildings of George Post within the collection are St. Paul's Building, Produce Exchange, Cotton Exchange, Union Trust Building, Mortimer Building, Equitable Building, Dry Dock Savings Bank, Mills Building, and the Western Union Building, among many others. This subseries includes a portrait of George Post.
    - miscellaneous buildings portrait (Box 55)
  - UNITED STATES
    This subseries contains negatives of copy prints of buildings in the United States arranged alphabetically by state and thereunder by city.
    - California
      - Los Angeles San Francisco (Box 56)
    - Colorado
      - Denver (Box 56)
    - District of Columbia
      - District of Columbia (Box 56)
    - Illinois
      - Chicago (Box 56)
    - Indiana
      - Fort Wayne (Box 57)
    - Iowa
      - Mason City (Box 57)
    - Louisiana
      - New Orleans (Box 57)
    - Maryland
      - Baltimore (Box 57)
    - Massachusetts
      - Boston Lowell Worcester (Box 57)
    - Michigan
      - Detroit (Box 58)
    - Minnesota
      - Duluth Minneapolis St. Paul (Box 58)
    - Missouri
      - Kansas City St. Louis (Box 58)
    - New Jersey
      - Newark (Box 58)
    - New York
      - Albany Brooklyn Buffalo Elmira (Box 58)
    - North Carolina
      - Asheville (Box 58)
    - Ohio
      - Canton Cleveland Columbus (Box 59)
    - Oklahoma
      - Bartlesville (Box 59)
    - Oregon
      - Portland (Box 59)
    - Pennsylvania
      - Bear-Run Erie Philadelphia Pittsburgh (Box 59)
    - Rhode Island
      - Providence (Box 59)
    - Tennessee
      - Nashville (Box 59)
    - Utah
      - Salt Lake City (Box 59)
    - Washington
      - Seattle Tacoma (Box 59)
  - INTERNATIONAL (by country)
    This subseries is negatives of copy prints of international cities arranged alphabetically by the name of the country.
    - Austria Belgium Canada Dominican Republic France Germany Greece Italy United Kingdom (Box 60)
- Series III Card Files
  This series consists of 4 x 6 file cards with information considered important by Weisman about a particular building or building type. Most of these cards are of a bibliographic nature with quotes and sources listed on the card, filed under approximate date of the building construction, predominantly for buildings in New York City, Philadelphia, Chicago, and Boston. The cards have been left in Weisman's original order with his original category titles (additional descriptions are given in brackets), with the exception of a miscellaneous box subsequently placed within this original arrangement. There are small 3 ½ x 5 inch photos scattered among the note cards, almost of all of which are available in the mounted copy prints and negative series. These prints are with the appropriate description of the building. Less than one quarter of the cards have an accompanying print.
  This series is further divided into four subseries. The first subseries has the card files for New York, Philadelphia, Chicago, and Boston. Miscellaneous Philadelphia cards are also found in subseries four. The second subseries has cards on general building types. The third subseries has cards on countries outside the United States, and the fourth has cards on American cities.
  - NEW YORK, PHILADELPHIA, CHICAGO, BOSTON
    - ca. 17th century -- 1851 (Box 61)
    - 1852 -- 1858 (Box 62)
    - 1859 -- 1884 (Box 63)
    - 1885 -- 1901 (Box 64)
    - 1902 -- 1958 undated (Box 65)
      See also Box 66 (for Boston and Philadelphia)
  - BUILDING TYPES
    - architectural styles - general hotels motels railway stations garage and service stations radio and television stations (Box 65)
    - factories cast iron front buildings (Box 66)
  - INTERNATIONAL CITIES
    - Greece Rome [ancient] English [United Kingdom] Flanders [Belgium] France Germany Italy Holland [Netherlands] Spain miscellaneous architecture negatives (Box 66)
  - AMERICAN CITIES
    - Philadelphia, PA [miscellaneous] Chicago, IL Minneapolis, MN St. Louis, MN San Francisco, CA Boston, MA Providence, RI Kansas City, MO Los Angeles, CA Pittsburgh, PA miscellaneous [predominantly Baltimore, MD] general architecture cards (Box 66)
- Series IV. Project Soho
  This series consists of the records of Project Soho, an architectural and cultural study commissioned by Pennsylvania State University and funded by a grant from the National Science Foundation. The records date from 1970, the year of the grant application, through 1973. The initial purpose of the project, as put forward by Dr. Weisman, was to provide the necessary research to create an historical account of what was formerly a fine urban commercial district that had since deteriorated, but was capable of being restored to its original condition. He wanted to preserve a part of unique American architectural history that had no counterpart anywhere. Weisman's students wrote the reports and took the photos. Credit for individual work is arranged within the work in the reports.
  Dr. Weisman and his students looked at the primary and secondary sources of art historians, sociologists, cultural geographers, economists, architectural engineers, and urban historians to discover the factors which shaped the character of the Soho district. A number of these student reports and some primary sources used by these students exist as reports within this series. All of the original grant funding proposals are also available giving detailed information concerning all the participants in this project and their aims.
  Detailed building information sheets covering the entire Soho district form the bulk of this series. Information available for each building includes alterations made since the date of construction. Much of this information was derived from the original building application filed at the time of construction. It covers both financial and architectural information. Most of these data sheets have an accompanying photograph of the building. The data forms, with accompanying print, are the most unique aspect of this series.
  The remainder of this series is made up of photos that document the entire area of Soho. 5 x 8 inch copy prints are filed by street address and span all of this cast iron district covering the area bordered by West Broadway, West Houston, Crosby and Canal Streets. Also available are the prints and negatives of the rolls of film as taken by the students. There are cross-indexed indices to guide the way through these prints. These include the originals of the 5 x 8 prints, as well as difficult to read prints of original architects' drawings and various specific details of the buildings, including windows, doors, and ornaments. Many of these prints are available in the series of mounted copy prints.
  This project was, in a great part, responsible for the designation of Soho as the SoHo Cast Iron Historic District. The Soho Cast Iron Historic District has 139 iron fronted buildings, all of which are represented in this series.
  This series is divided into three subseries: information forms, reports, and copy prints.
  - INFORMATION FORMS
    This subseries consists of information forms from Project Soho arranged alphabetically by street name and, within that arrangement by street number and side of street, e.g. east side of Broadway and then the west side of Broadway, and north side of Broome Street followed by the south side of Broome Street. Depending on the street, all the even numbered street addresses will be followed by all the odd numbered streets addresses or vice versa.
    - 420 -- 430 Broadway, east side (Box 67, Folder 715)
    - 434 -- 458 Broadway, east side (Box 67, Folder 716)
    - 460 -- 486 Broadway, east side (Box 67, Folder 717)
    - 488 -- 528 Broadway, east side (Box 67, Folder 718)
    - 530 -- 566 Broadway, east side (Box 67, Folder 719)
    - 568 -- 602 Broadway, east side (Box 67, Folder 720)
    - 419 -- 429 Broadway, west side (Box 68, Folder 721)
    - 433 -- 461 Broadway, west side (Box 68, Folder 722)
    - 465 -- 487 Broadway, west side (Box 68, Folder 723)
    - 489 -- 527 Broadway, west side (Box 68, Folder 724)
    - 529 -- 567 Broadway, west side (Box 68, Folder 725)
    - 569 -- 601 Broadway, west side (Box 68, Folder 726)
    - 436 -- 438 Broome Street, north side (Box 69, Folder 727)
    - 442 -- 468 Broome Street, north side (Box 69, Folder 728)
    - 470 -- 482 Broome Street, north side (Box 69, Folder 729)
    - 484 -- 519 Broome Street, north side (Box 69, Folder 730)
    - 429 -- 437 Broome Street, south side (Box 69, Folder 731)
    - 453 -- 467 Broome Street, south side (Box 69, Folder 732)
    - 469 -- 479 Broome Street, south side (Box 69, Folder 733)
    - 483 -- 499 Broome Street, south side (Box 69, Folder 734)
    - 251 -- 289 Canal Street, north side (Box 70, Folder 735)
    - 301 -- 311 Canal Street, north side (Box 70, Folder 736)
    - 313 -- 331 Canal Street, north side (Box 70, Folder 737)
    - 335 -- 357 Canal Street, north side (Box 70, Folder 738)
    - 359 -- 375 Canal Street. north side (Box 70, Folder 739)
    - 2 -- 140 Crosby, west side (Box 70, Folder 740)
    - 54 -- 70 Grand Street, north side (Box 71, Folder 741)
    - 72 -- 80 Grand Street, north side (Box 71, Folder 742)
    - 90 -- 104 Grand Street, north side (Box 71, Folder 743)
    - 53 -- 69 Grand Street, south side (Box 71, Folder 744)
    - 71 -- 87 Grand Street, south side (Box 71, Folder 745)
    - 89 -- 105 Grand Street, south side (Box 71, Folder 746)
    - 107 -- 115 Grand Street, south side (Box 71, Folder 747)
    - 1 -- 36 Greene Street, east side (Box 72, Folder 748)
    - 38 -- 52 Greene Street, east side (Box 72, Folder 749)
    - 58 -- 86 Greene Street, east side (Box 72, Folder 750)
    - 90 -- 122 Greene Street, east side (Box 72, Folder 751)
    - 128 -- 149 Greene Street, east side (Box 72, Folder 752)
    - 7 -- 31 Greene Street, west side (Box 73, Folder 753)
    - 33 -- 55 Greene Street, west side (Box 73, Folder 754)
    - 57 -- 83 Greene Street, west side (Box 73, Folder 755)
    - 91 -- 117 Greene Street, west side (Box 73, Folder 756)
    - 121 -- 143 Greene Street, west side (Box 73, Folder 757)
    - 31 -- 37 Howard Street, south side (Box 73, Folder 758)
    - 30 -- 38 Howard Street, north side (Box 73, Folder 759)
    - 51 -- 53 Leonard Street (Box 73, Folder 760)
    - 16 -- 36 Mercer Street, east side (Box 74, Folder 761)
    - 66 -- 96 Mercer Street, east side (Box 74, Folder 762)
    - 142 -- 172 Mercer Street, east side (Box 74, Folder 763)
    - 1 -- 35 Mercer Street, west side (Box 74, Folder 764)
    - 41 -- 79 Mercer Street, west side (Box 74, Folder 765)
    - 81 -- 121 Mercer Street, west side (Box 74, Folder 766)
    - 123 -- 172 Mercer Street, west side (Box 74, Folder 767)
    - 93 -- 107 Prince Street, north side (Box 75, Folder 768)
    - 109 -- 125 Prince Street, north side (Box 75, Folder 769)
    - 129 -- 143 Prince Street, north side (Box 75, Folder 770)
    - 72 -- 90 Prince Street, south side (Box 75, Folder 771)
    - 94 -- 106 Prince Street, south side (Box 75, Folder 772)
    - 110 -- 126 Prince Street, south side (Box 75, Folder 773)
    - 128 -- 140 Prince Street, south side (Box 75, Folder 774)
    - 106 -- 108 Reade Street (Box 75, Folder 775)
    - 79 -- 83 Spring Street, north side (Box 76, Folder 776)
    - 91 -- 101 Spring Street, north side (Box 76, Folder 777)
    - 107 -- 121 Spring Street, north side (Box 76, Folder 778)
    - 127 -- 141 Spring Street, north side (Box 76, Folder 779)
    - 143 -- 157 Spring Street, north side (Box 76, Folder 780)
    - 80 -- 124 Spring Street, south side (Box 76, Folder 781)
    - 126 -- 140 Spring Street, south side (Box 76, Folder 782)
    - 146 -- 162 Spring Street, south side (Box 76, Folder 783)
    - 305 -- 331 West Broadway, east side (Box 77, Folder 784)
    - 339 -- 361 West Broadway, east side (Box 77, Folder 785)
    - 375 -- 399 West Broadway, east side (Box 77, Folder 786)
    - 407 -- 435 West Broadway, east side (Box 77, Folder 787)
    - 445 -- 475 West Broadway, east side (Box 77, Folder 788)
    - 308 -- 310 West Broadway, west side (Box 77, Folder 789)
    - 338 -- 404 West Broadway, west side (Box 77, Folder 790)
    - 420 -- 438 West Broadway, west side (Box 77, Folder 791)
    - 458 -- 482 West Broadway, west side (Box 77, Folder 792)
    - 2 -- 26 Wooster Street, east side (Box 78, Folder 793)
    - 38 -- 50 Wooster Street, east side (Box 78, Folder 794)
    - 69 -- 90 Wooster Street, east side (Box 78, Folder 795)
    - 98 -- 128 Wooster Street, east side (Box 78, Folder 796)
    - 134 -- 158 Wooster Street, east side (Box 78, Folder 797)
    - 3 -- 27 Wooster Street, west side (Box 78, Folder 798)
    - 31 -- 55 Wooster Street, west side (Box 78, Folder 799)
    - 61 -- 83 Wooster Street, west side (Box 78, Folder 800)
    - 95 -- 121 Wooster Street, west side (Box 78, Folder 801)
    - 130 -- 155 Wooster Street, west side (Box 78, Folder 802)
    - 5 Worth Street (Box 78, Folder 803)
  - REPORTS
    This subseries consists of written reports for Project Soho.
    - reports for Soho Seminar by L. Vitello (Box 79, Folder 804)
    - NSF report-- grant request (Box 79, Folder 805)
    - NSF report-- Sociology, History and Economic Development of Soho (Box 79, Folder 806)
    - NSF report-- Zucker, Smith, Snook, Dileo, Poeter, Fernbach (Box 79, Folder 807)
    - Soho Art History Report by W. Leininger (Box 79, Folder 808)
    - 1963 South Houston Industrial Area report by Chester Rapkin (Box 79, Folder 809)
  - PROJECT SOHO COPY PRINTS
    The third subseries is the copy prints of Project Soho and it is further divided into seven sub-subseries. This arrangement conforms to Weisman's arrangement as set up in his indices. These indices are the first sub-subseries and provide thorough cross-indexing for all the copy prints. The second sub-subseries is 5 x 8 copy prints arranged alphabetically by street name and side of street (e.g. Broadway, east side). The third sub-subseries is the 35mm film prints of the front of the Soho buildings arranged by roll numbers one through forty-two, based on the Weisman index. The fourth sub-subseries is the 120mm film print copies of original architects' drawings arranged by roll number A through Z, from the Weisman index. The fifth sub-subseries is the 35mm film prints of original architects' drawings arranged by roll number AA to EE in order to maintain the order of the Weisman index. The sixth sub-subseries is 120 mm film of specific details of Soho buildings arranged by roll number HB (1) through to HB (6), also to correspond to the Weisman index. The seventh, and final, sub-subseries consists of miscellaneous Soho prints that were a part of Project Soho.
    - Indices
      - index to buildings by architect, date, materials (Box 80, Folder 810)
      - index to photographs (Box 80, Folder 811)
      - index to photographs copy (Box 80, Folder 812)
      - Soho photo notes (Box 80, Folder 813)
      - index cards -- building photographs by address (Box 81)
    - Soho Prints
      - Broadway -- east side, evens (Box 82, Folder 814)
      - Broadway -- west side, odds (Box 82, Folder 815)
      - Broome Street -- north side, evens, south side, odds (Box 82, Folder 816)
      - Canal Street -- north side, odds (Box 82, Folder 817)
      - Grand Street -- north side, evens (Box 82, Folder 818)
      - Grand Street -- south side, odds (Box 82, Folder 819)
      - Greene Street -- east side, evens (Box 82, Folder 820)
      - Greene Street -- west side, odds (Box 82, Folder 821)
      - Howard Street -- north and south sides (Box 82, Folder 822)
      - Mercer Street -- east side, evens (Box 82, Folder 823)
      - Mercer Street -- west side, odds (Box 82, Folder 824)
      - Prince Street -- north side, odds (Box 82, Folder 825)
      - Prince Street -- south side, evens (Box 82, Folder 826)
      - Spring Street -- north side, odds (Box 82, Folder 827)
      - Spring Street -- south side, evens (Box 82, Folder 828)
      - Wooster Street -- west side, odds (Box 82, Folder 829)
    - 35mm film prints
      - "(35) 1": 131 Prince Street 62 -- 98, 130 -- 156 Wooster Street, east side (Box 83, Folder 832)
      - "(35) 2": 145 -- 149 Spring Street, north side 450 -- 500 Broome Street, north side (Box 83, Folder 833)
      - "(35) 3": 468 -- 478 West Broadway, west side (Box 83, Folder 834)
      - "(35) 4": 411 -- 465 West Broadway, east side (Box 83, Folder 835)
      - "(35) 5": 101 -- 141 Prince Street, north side (Box 83, Folder 836)
      - "(35) 6": 85 -- 191 Spring Street, north side (Box 83, Folder 837)
      - "(35) 7": 55 -- 69 Mercer Street, west side 560 -- 566 Broadway, east side 35 -- 45 Wooster Street, west side (Box 83, Folder 838)
      - "(35) 8": 161 -- 411 West Broadway, east side (Box 83, Folder 839)
      - "(35) 9": 43 -- 99 Wooster, west side 100 -- 126 Wooster, east side (Box 83, Folder 840)
      - "(35) 10": 70 -- 72 Grand Street, north side 480 -- 494 Broome Street, north side 15 -- 25 Greene Street, west side (Box 83, Folder 841)
      - "(35) 11": 438 -- 448 Broome Street, north side 60 -- 118 Grand Street, north side (Box 83, Folder 842)
      - "(35) 12": 83 -- 87 Spring Street, north side 30 -- 52 Howard Street, north side 54 Grand Street, north side 261 -- 305 Canal Street, north side (Box 83, Folder 843)
      - "(35) 13": 305 -- 375 Canal Street, north side 6 -- 18 Greene Street, east side (Box 83, Folder 844)
      - "(35) 14": 18 -- 70 Greene Street, east side (Box 83, Folder 845)
      - "(35) 15": 99 -- 143 Greene Street, west side (Box 83, Folder 846)
      - "(35) 16": 96 -- 150 Greene Street, east side (Box 83, Folder 847)
      - "(35) 17": 427 -- 429, 503 - 511 Broadway, west side 9 -- 47 Mercer Street, west side 83 -- 87 Grand Street, south side 465 -- 475 Broome, south side (Box 83, Folder 848)
      - "(35) 18": 546 -- 716 Broadway, east side 72 -- 82 Greene Street, east side (Box 83, Folder 849)
      - "(35) 19": 12 -- 106 Wooster Street, east side (Box 83, Folder 850)
      - "(35) 20": 458 -- 556 Broadway, east side (Box 83, Folder 851)
      - "(35) 21": 53 -- 91 Grand Street, south side 7 -- 13 Mercer Street, west side (Box 83, Folder 852)
      - "(35) 22": 19 -- 87 Mercer Street, west side 43 -- 47 Grand Street, south side (Box 83, Folder 853)
      - "(35) 23": 426 -- 458 Broadway, east side 16 -- 60 Mercer Street, east side (Box 84, Folder 84)
      - "(35) 24": 131 -- 169 Mercer Street, west side (Box 84, Folder 855)
      - "(35) 25": 93 -- 125 Mercer Street, west side (Box 84, Folder 856)
      - "(35) 26": 83 -- 85 Spring Street, north side 64 -- 112 Mercer Street, east side (Box 84, Folder 857)
      - "(35) 27": 116 -- 172 Mercer Street, east side (Box 84, Folder 858)
      - "(35) 28": 67 -- 157 Wooster Street, west side (Box 84, Folder 859)
      - "(35) 29": 29 -- 67 Wooster Street, west side 19 -- 49 Greene Street, west side (Box 84, Folder 860)
      - "(35) 30": 47 -- 99 Greene Street, west side (Box 84, Folder 861)
      - "(35) 31": 105 -- 143 Greene Street, west side (Box 84, Folder 862)
      - "(35) 32": 545 -- 601 Broadway, west side (Box 84, Folder 863)
      - "(35) 33": 473 -- 545 Broadway, west side (Box 84, Folder 864)
      - "(35) 34": 425 -- 471 Broadway, west side 106 -- 108 Reade Street 5 Worth Street 51 -- 53 Leonard Street 95 -- 97 Grand Street, south side (Box 84, Folder 865)
      - "(35) 35": 107 -- 131 Grand Street, south side 11 -- 31 Howard Street, south side (Box 84, Folder 866)
      - "(35) 36": 33 -- 47 Howard Street, south side 465 -- 497 Broome Street, south side (Box 84, Folder 867)
      - "(35) 37": 429 -- 463 Broome Street, south side (Box 84, Folder 868)
      - "(35) 38": 114 -- 156 Spring Street, south side (Box 84, Folder 869)
      - "(35) 39": 96 -- 106 Spring Street, south side 112 -- 124 Prince Street, south side (Box 84, Folder 870)
      - "(35) 40": 72 -- 108 Prince Street, south side 561 -- 567 Broadway, west side (Box 84, Folder 871)
      - "(35) 41": 20 -- 96 Crosby Street, west side (Box 84, Folder 872)
      - "(35) 42": 88 -- 102 Prince Street, south side 16 Crosby Street, west side 132 -- 138 Lafayette Street (Box 84, Folder 873)
    - 120 mm film prints of original architect's drawings
      - rolls A and B: plans of 74 Grand Street, 486 Broadway, 477-79 Broadway (50 -- 52 Mercer Street) (Box 85, Folder 874)
      - roll C: plans of 477 -- 479 Broadway (50 -- 52 Mercer Street), 486 Broadway, 39 -- 41 Wooster Street (Box 85, Folder 875)
      - roll D: plans of 14 -- 16 Wooster Street, 359 Canal Street, 8 Greene Street, 444 Broadway, 104 Grand Street, 359 West Broadway (495 Broome Street) (Box 85, Folder 876)
      - roll E: plans of 91 -- 93 Mercer Street, 60 Grand Street, 83 -- 87 Grand Street (Box 85, Folder 877)
      - roll F: plans of 83 -- 87 Grand Street, 542 -- 544 Broadway, 361 Canal Street, 107 -- 113 Grand Street (32 Mercer Street), 64 -- 68 Wooster (Box 85, Folder 878)
      - roll G: plans of 64 -- 68 Wooster Street, 89 Grand Street, 329 -- 331 Canal Street (6 Greene Street), 458 Broadway (123 Grand Street) (Box 85, Folder 879)
      - roll H: plans of 458 Broadway (123 Grand Street), 79 Mercer Street, 27 Howard Street, 428 -- 432 Broadway (37 -- 39 Howard Street) (Box 85, Folder 880)
      - roll I: plans of 428 -- 432 Broadway (37 -- 39 Howard Street), 114 -- 116 Spring Street (Box 85, Folder 881)
      - roll J: plans of 158 Wooster Street, 8 Greene Street, 15 -- 17 Greene Street (Box 85, Folder 882)
      - roll K: plans of 37 -- 61 West Houston, 169 Mercer Street, 15 --21 Wooster Street, 568 -- 578 Broadway (Box 85, Folder 883)
      - roll L: plans of 568 -- 578 Broadway, 90 Wooster Street (140 Spring Street), 331 -- 335 West Broadway, 155 -- 157 Mercer Street (Box 85, Folder 884)
      - roll M: plans of 155 -- 157 Mercer Street, 152 -- 156 Wooster Street, 105 -- 113 Wooster Street, 131 -- 135 Prince Street (Box 85, Folder 885)
      - roll N: plans of 131 -- 135 Prince Street, 434 -- 448 Broadway, 530 Broadway (Box 85, Folder 886)
      - roll O: plans of 434 -- 438 Broadway, 127 Spring Street, 117 -- 119 Mercer Street, 145 -- 148 Wooster Street (Box 85, Folder 887)
      - roll P: plans of 146 -- 148 Wooster Street, 155 -- 157 Mercer Street, 583 -- 587 Broadway, 142 -- 144 Wooster Street, 138 -- 140 Greene Street (Box 85, Folder 888)
      - roll Q: plans of 132 -- 140 Greene Street, 115 -- 121 Prince Street (Box 85, Folder 889)
      - roll R: plans of 115 -- 121 Prince Street, 124 -- 126 Wooster Street, 27 Howard Street, 453 West Broadway (Box 85, Folder 890)